

# **Tufan Recep SARI**

# Frontend Developer



+90 534 830 56 67



www.linkedin.com/in/tufan-sari



tufanrsari@gmail.com



https://github.com/tufansari

#### **SUMMARY**

I have experience at web software languages. The software languages and skills I know are as follows. I have focus on web frontend, so improving javascript's libraries, frameworks and trying to carry higher level. I also have experience in education. That's why I believe I'm good at relationships and communication with people. I will adapt to your vision and try to move forward. In addition to, optimistic and personable individual enthusiastic about meeting new people. Strong presentation skills and a real researcher.

#### CAREER

- STILL
- 20.01.2023

# Abb Garjan Group

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- UI design with specific frameworks like Material
  UI and DevExpress.
- Creating reusable components and making them ready to use web services APIs and UX.
- 11.10.2022
- 11.05.2022

Smartpro Academy

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

- Full stack development.
- Intern.

## • 2020-2021

#### **HUMAN RELATIONS OFFICER**

**Enthoosia** 

• Provide operation management and flow.

• 2017-2018

# **TEACHER**

Capa Science High School

- Administered assessments to determine each student's specific edicational and social needs.
   Kept students on-task with proactive behavior modification and positive reinforcement strategies.
- Prepared quizzes, tests and examinations to gauge how well students were learning.

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaScript
- RESTful API
- SASS & SCSS
- AzureDevOps

- TypeScript
- UI Design
- HTML
- Postman

- React.js
- Material UI
- CSS
- Firebase

- Node.js
- Tailwind
- C#
- MS Sql

- JQuer
- JQueryBootstrap
- ASP.NET MVC

#### **ONLINE COURSES**

HTTP Networking Course – Fetch and REST APIs in JavaScript/ freeCodeCamp.org

React, Redux and Hooks bootcamp/ Engin Demirog

Web programming with React / Turkcell-Gelecegi Yazanlar.

C# Programming camp / Engin Demirog

#### **EDUCATION**

• 2019

#### **PEDAGOGY**

Marmara University • Master's Degree.

• 2014-2018

#### **BIOLOGY TEACHER EDUCATION**

Marmara University • Bachelor's Degree.

## **LANGUAGES**

#### **ENGLISH**

- TALK
- Upper intermediate.
- WRITING
- Advanced.

#### **TURKISH**

• Native Language.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate,

Exam: Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure,

React 101.

# **REFERENCES**

Orhan Umit Keskin - Product Owner at AnnounceKit

+90 (530) 667 06 19

Cihan Kilinckaya - Manager at Apple

+90 (532) 280 47 35

Tugay Aydin - Software Instructor

+90 (542) 332 14 52